{
  "chapter1": {
    "q1": {
      "prompt": "What are the main jobs of an OS?",
      "distractors": ["Manage resources", "Control programs", "Manage the hardware and give them power", "Schdule tasks"],
      "answer": ["Manage resources and control programs."]
    },
    "q2": {
      "prompt": "Order the memory hierarcy from fastest to slowest.",
      "distractors": [
        "registers, main memory, cache, non-volitile memory, SDD, HDD, optical disk, magnegtic tape",
        "non-volitile memory, SDD, HDD, optical disk, magnegtic tape, registers, main memory, cache",
        "magnegtic tape, optical disk, HDD, SDD, non-volitile memory, main memory, cache, registers,",
        "registers, cache, non-volitile memory, HDD, SDD, magnegtic tape, optical disk, main memory"],
      "answer": ["registers, cache, main memory non-volitile memory, SDD, HDD, optical disk, magnegtic tape"]
    },
    "q3": {
      "prompt": "Which type of multiprocessing has a boss worker relationship?",
      "distractors": [
        "Symmetric Multi-Processing"
        ],
      "answer": ["Asymmetric Multi-Processing"]
    },
    "q4": {
      "prompt": "What is the part of an operating system called that runs all the time?",
      "distractors": [
        "Microsoft Edge",
        "Window Manager",
        "Scheduler",
        "Interrupt",
        "CPU",
        "Process Manager"],
      "answer": ["Kernal"]
    },
    "q5": {
      "prompt": "Which is NOT a basic component of a Computer System",
      "distractors": [
        "Device Controller",
        "CPU",
        "Shared Memory",
        "Common Bus"],
      "answer": ["Network Adapter"]
    },
    "q6": {
      "prompt": "What is the name for the instructions that are executed when a certain event happens such as a keyboard key being pressed?",
      "distractors": [
        "Kernel",
        "Catch and Dispatch",
        "Interrupt Vector",
        "Interrupt Signal"
      ],
      "answer": ["Interrupt Service Routine"]
    },
    "q7": {
      "prompt": "Memory is considered non-volatile because its data disappears when the power is cut off.",
      "distractors": [
        "True"
      ],
      "answer": ["False"]
    },
    "q8": {
      "prompt": "Fault tolerance is one of the key advantages of a multi-processor system over a single- processor system.",
      "distractors": [
        "False"
      ],
      "answer": ["True"]
    },
    "q9": {
      "prompt": "Which type of processor configurations makes a shared cache on the CPU possible?",
      "distractors": [
        "Symmetric",
        "Single Chip",
        "Multi-chip",
        "Clustered"
      ],
      "answer": ["Multi-core"]
    },
    "q10": {
      "prompt": "What is the main purpose of having DMA?",
      "distractors": [
        "Utilize multile CPU's for efficiency.",
        "Device drivers are abvle to use less cache",
        "Enhance security of data while being transferred",
        "DMA isn't a thing"
      ],
      "answer": ["Reduce the burden on the CPU for performing I/O"]
    },
    "q11": {
      "prompt": "What is the main purpose of having DMA?",
      "distractors": [
        "Utilize multile CPU's for efficiency.",
        "Device drivers are abvle to use less cache",
        "Enhance security of data while being transferred",
        "DMA isn't a thing"
      ],
      "answer": ["Reduce the burden on the CPU for performing I/O"]
    },
    "q12": {
      "prompt": "What is the startup process called to get the Operating System running when a computer is turned on?",
      "distractors": [
        "Asymmetric Startup",
        "Interrupt Service Routine",
        "Multiprocessing",
        "Multitasking"
      ],
      "answer": ["Bootstrapping"]
    },
    "q13": {
      "prompt": "Which of the following is NOT one of the resource management responsibilites of the OS?",
      "distractors": [
        "Process Management",
        "Memory Management",
        "File System Management",
        "Mass Storage Management",
        "Cache Management",
        "I/O Subsystem Management"
      ],
      "answer": ["None of the Above"]
    },
    "q14": {
      "prompt": "What security term describes ensuring that data is correct, authentic, and reliable?",
      "distractors": [
        "Safeguard",
        "Availability",
        "Protection",
        "Confidentiality"
      ],
      "answer": ["Integrity"]
    },
    "q15": {
      "prompt": "Mounting and Unmounting are part of File System Management.",
      "distractors": [
        "True"
      ],
      "answer": ["False"]
    },
    "q16": {
      "prompt": "What is the command used in a Linux shell to display the current working directory path?",
      "distractors": [
        "ls",
        "PATH",
        "cd",
        "echo"
      ],
      "answer": ["pwd"]
    },
    "q17": {
      "prompt": "Which is NOT one of the three main categories of User Interfaces for an OS?",
      "distractors": [
        "Command Line",
        "GUI",
        "Touch"
      ],
      "answer": ["Voice"]
    }
  },

  "chapter2": {

  },

  "chapter3": {

  }
}
